Director Mohongjin
mom
I told you to not wait.
Ta-da!
It's not as good as pizza.
But it's your favorite, sticky rice cake.
It resembles you.
No it doesn't.
Is it tasty?
This cosmos flower is way bigger than
the one we saw yesterday.
But mom, don't bring me more.
They must feel pain, too.
Let's go
Ta-da!
Speaking practice time
You have to do it
even if you don't want to.
You have to be able to converse
with people who don't know sign language.
It's too hard and embarrassing.
You still have to do it.
Dad isn't around anymore.
When I'm not around, what will you do?
You would be so sad
if I had to take a break from school.
Right? Let's do it.
Let's practice again.
Hello
You should continue the conversation
and respond with
"It's nice to meet you."
It's nice to meet you.
What is your name?
Kwon Kyung sook
Mom, you are doing so well.
Dad's hospital bills all the loans.
We paid it all back.
And now I'm healthy, too.
Can't you quit your part-time job?
I wish you could
just focus on your studies.
I don't work for the money.
It's fun!
I'm fine.
Mom, drink this often.
You really should, alright?
Did I not brew it right?
Mom
Are you alright?
Did you kiss? Did you?
Wow
Hey, Did Yunyoung pass her
government employee test?
No, she failed
Korean history just by a few points.
Wow. Then, she'll definitely
pass next time, right?
You bet!
But can you take
the government employee test
Without graduating high school?
How many times do I have to tell you
The test doesn't have degree requirements?
Our cutie doesn't remember anything
other than food, right?
Eat up.
Now that you say it, I remembered.
What is it?
I came prepared.
Oh, you have good sense.
She's coming. Hide it.
I told you guys not to eat
outside food here.
The smell is distracting to
the other customers.
Sis, This is food.
And this is food, too.
You can't discriminate.
If my boss finds out, I'll get in trouble.
Sis, The boss here is really nice
Everyone knows that
Right.
Sis, sit down for a second.
Your mom, she really doesn't know
you're not back at school?
So you're not going to enroll again?
Why would she? It's unnecessary.
Yunyoung is so smart
she can just take the GED.
Right
That's true.
Alright. This is our present.
Next time, you will certainly pass
and become a government employee.
Eat slowly and make sure to chew.
- You can do it!
- Fighting!
Yunyoung, do you want YEOT
for good luck?
Mom!
Did you get really hurt?
No, it's just a little bit.
But you still got hurt.
I'm sorry, I'll be careful
Promise to be careful.
Please watch out for my mom.
And please let me know if anything happens.
Okay. The hospital said that she's okay
So don't worry too much.
Alright. Thank you.
Let's go.
Kyungsook
Easy does it.
My pretty mom, I'll be a little late,
So don't wait for me our side. Stay home!
Yunyoung looks like her mother.
Younyoung keeps getting prettier
Because she resembles you,
She looks like her dad
that's where her good looks come from
I don't know what you're saying
But now that she's no longer a minor
before she graduates, marry her to me.
There aren't men like me around
I will make her happy every night.
Don't joke around about my daughter!
I guess she understood that part.
Yunyoung
Hello, sir.
Can I get one iced coffee?
Of course. You're so kind to my mom,
so this one is on the house.
But what are you doing here at this hour?
I went to the glasses store,
and stopped by on the way home
I see, let me go get your drink.
You can take your time.
Yunyoung
Your mother must be worried.
You're smart
So, you should know better.
If you report me,
I will kill your mother.
Oh wait,
It's been awhile since that
crippled father of yours died.
Maybe I should make her
feel like a woman before I kill her.
Like I did to you.
Yunyoung…
Yunyoung
I suddenly miss kyungsook.
You should eat a little
The body is too badly damaged to
call this a voluntary manslaughter.
You could've hit him without killing him.
Look, don't take me wrong.
I'm not saying you did it.
Let's say the two of you had
some sort of an agreement.
Whether it was about money,
or taking care of your mom.
If he was still alive
we could do cross interrogation or use a
lie detector test to find out the truth
There's no case where murder is
accepted as an act of self-defense.
An act of retaliation
cannot fall under self-defense.
And if we want the self-defense ruling,
We would have to prove the sexual assault.
The two of you knew each other,
And kept in contact often
because of your mother.
So the evidence from
the scene isn't enough.
Plus, the perpetrator is dead.
The legal matters are very complicated.
I don't care as long
as my mother isn't hurt.
Your mother may suffer even more
When you get sentenced.
Even if you appeal, you have to
go to jail before and during trial.
And you don't have student identification.
Your birthday has passed, too,
So most likely, you won't
be tried as a juvenile,
you will have to go to prison.
Why don't we go public
and get help from women's
rights organizations
or social organizations?
I'm scared of the attention.
I don't want to do that.
Mom
look at me.
I have a favor to ask of you.
Please do it for me.
Mom, don't do anything for me.
Even if someone says they
will help us, don't accept it.
I'm already exhausted by people
around me and at school watching me.
I don't want the world
to look at us with pity.
I wouldn't be able to stand that.
I...
I killed a man.
It wasn't your fault!
Some people will point at
me and call me a murderer.
Mom, I don't think
I'll be able to stand it.
I will announce the verdict.
Case number 2017 Hight Court Agreement 174.
Defendant
Jung Yunyoung.
We need the words
of the perpetrator of the
sexual assault committed
against the defendant.
But due to the
death of Kim Chulmin
The case leads to lack of evidence.
This attack and retaliation cannot be
looked at as an act of self-defense.
However, there are other factors
to take into account, and thus,
The defendant Jung Yunyoung is
Sentenced to five years.
She's got 5
Mom
No
Time to report.
She looks pretty.
Tell me your name, crime and sentence.
My...
Name is…
We'll hear from the new girl later.
She looks like she's going to faint.
But shouldn't she still report?
Put down your things and rest.
Hey! I told you not to touch!!
Hey, don't.
I said, don't this bitch!
Starting up again!
Don't!
Wait wait!
Are you okay? She has anger management
issues. She keeps blowing up.
You okay?
Woah, she's bleeding.
I'm fine.
Oh dear…
Hey!
Because of your spit it
will get more infected.
Gross!
What? It won't get infected!
Spit heals everything.
Is that why your face looks like that?
Shut the fuck up!
My face is well taken care
of, no thanks to you! Back off!!
Oh God, my arm.
Big Sis.
Please pray for her.
She was crying all night.
You can pray for her.
I'd feel like I'm sinning
even more if I pray, so I can't.
You're not afraid of sinning,
you're just afraid you'll feel
more guilt. That's why you can't.
Oh…
Wipe it.
So weak! Only your
tongue working out, huh?
Go down! One, two.
Be careful. Free supplies.
The soap will give your face mold.
The toothbrush will rot your teeth.
The towel will make your face blotchy.
The socks have so little material
it will give you athlete's foot.
Cut the crap will you?
If you want to give them to
her, just do it without the bullshit.
You just do your reading.
If she weren't my jail roommate,
I would've killed her alrelady.
Use them well.
Thank you.
You're pretty. You have baby skin,
And you're young.
Lucky you, huh?
Since we have a new family member,
let's have a feast for breakfast!
We ate like this last night.
Also, this is all Haesoo's food.
Shut up and just eat
Will you, unless you want to go to
the doctor first thing in the morning.
You thief bitch!
What? You have a lot of money
outside from all your scam and fraud.
You have to give back in places like this.
You have to expiate a little.
You always talk of
expiation! Sick of it!
You guys are so simple and impulsive.
I'm just happy cause I'm eating for free.
Come here.
Wow.
Relax and eat up.
Whether in here or out there,
it's all the same. You'll manage.
Just go with the flow and mingle.
You learn this bitch is like this,
that bitch is like that.
Big Sis here used to be a teacher
So she speaks in a way
that's so easy to understand.
Penal labor is literally forced labor.
So since we have to work,
make sure you're full!
New one, where do you want to work?
Sarang, Rose that idiot
And Haesoo the idiot
all work at the repair shop
And Big Sis and I work
at the woodworking shop.
Big sis is really amazing
She is a death row inmate so
She doesn't have to work,
but she still does.
Shit I must be out of my mind
That big mouth!
Which place pays you best?
Huh?
The repair shop pays best,
but the work is shit.
You get hurt and bleed.
I'll do that one.
I have to earn money.
You're a level 4
so you won't be paid much.
Two to three dollars.
In one day?
In one month.
Hey, don't joke around.
You'll get 30-40 dollars a month.
Try out the repair shop.
Try other ones out, too.
Then decide what fits you best.
Okay.
But
You are you ranked higher?
Why is your uniform pink?
What? My clothes,
these!
She's a model prisoner,
Not on the catwalk but here in jail,
she's the good one.
I can't agree.
The world is so unfair,
whether it's here or out there!
How is that idiot a model prisoner?
Pink suits me so well.
Hey!
Stop talking nonsense.
Eat up, and get ready for work.
Yes, big sis. Should I
give you a chicken wing?
Hey there. Get back in line.
Go!
Move.
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven.
Twelve
Who are you?
Are you new?
Can you answer properly?
Yes, I am here to work.
What's your inmate number?
It is 2037.
Remember that number.
In here, that's your name and
social security.
Understood?
Yes, understood.
Learn the ropes from your roomates.
This is a very important component.
This is the propeller shaft.
Sometimes it's referred
to as rear-wheel drive.
You're getting in the way.
Go over to Sarang. Go!
Get lost.
Fuck, I said get lost!
Hey! Move.
I'm sick of this.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven
Eight, nine, ten, eleven
Twelve. Finished.
Excuse me?
What?
When do we get paid?
I don't know what shit you
heard before coming here,
but there's no pay here.
Did you think it's like real world here?
You expect to get paid?
You think the
hard-earned tax dollars of
Citizens are paid out to
you so you can spend it?
How dare you!
It's her first time.
Besides,
We do get paid for the work.
And on special occasions
if we make a request,
we can use that money as our
allowances to buy things in here.
Looking out for each other, huh?
Unless you want solitary
confinement, watch it.
Fuck!
I didn't do anything.
I told you already. Don't, ok?
You see that bell, look, look.
If you ever feel your life's in danger,
Run and press that button.
The guards will come save you.
You're exaggerating.
Why you brat!
I'm holding myself back.
Because I don't want to add
one years and serve life in here.
Why?
So you can leave and become a pimp?
What?
Are you being nice to the new one
So you can sell her once you're out?
How can you have such a filthy mouth?
Don't listen to her. It's all a lie.
Hey!
This girl is different from the rest of us.
You, bitch, belong here, but this one,
She's in here unfairly.
Is that so?
Then why are you writing
to the judge everyday?
I told you I'm holding myself back
Cos I don't want a life sentence.
You have no other future than being a pimp,
So why don't you kill
Haesoo and become a lifer?
That's what I'm saying.
These people. What's up with you guys!
Big sis!!
You come here, huh!
Let's just live here forever.
I'll make you a lifer.
Come on!
- I'll let you live here forever.
- Come on!
You with that prettey face of yours.
I was just joking around.
- I'll get rid of all your shine.
- I was just kidding
Why you snake.
I'm sorry but.
I'm really sorry but.
Can you guys please be quiet?
Child,
What's your name?
It's Yunyoung.
I had a son
A drunk driver hit and killed him,
and drove away.
So you know what I did?
The driver eventully turned
himself in, but I set his house on fire.
I ended up killing his five family
members who were asleep in the house.
When I'm awake,
my guilt chokes me.
When I'm asleep,
the people I killed choke me.
Don't hold it inside.
Write letters, pray,
do something, anything to let it out.
That's how you live on.
Mom
It's me, Yunyoung. You're not sick, right?
If you feel any pain,
go to the hospital.
Don't worry about the money.
And I'm doing well.
Everyone here is nice to me.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Did she get hit in the head with a hammer?
We need to send her to see the doctor.
She's adjusting quickly.
I...
Huh?
How can I send a letter?
You put your letter in an envelope
and then put a stamp on it.
I know that, but...
See that?
Hang your letter there.
The meal helpers
they'll take it and mail it out.
Here.
I'm not giving these for free.
Pay me back twofold
when you earn money.
Thank you!
The saw should be slightly above the wood,
And then push it. Let me show you.
Toilet paper!
I need toilet paper!
Korea history books
Do you like Korean history?
No.
If there's anything you like,
feel free to read it.
Thank you
Please.
Can't I please bring it?
I'm sorry.
Outside food is not allowed in.
Then, Can I just bring this?
I'm very sorry.
I wish I could help.
If you bring this in, not just me,
But your daughter can also get in trouble.
Okay. I won't.
I understand.
I'll just take it back.
One, two, three, four, five, six. Finished.
Get to your workplaces and don't be late!
2037!
Yes, 2037.
You have a visitor.
Mom is doing well and healthy...
Mom is well
Mom, why did you come all the way here?
Mom is
Well and healthy.
Is my daughter
Doing well?
Wow. Mom, you've practiced
speaking so much.
Hello
Mom, you have to
continue the conversation.
You have to say,
"It's nice to meet you."
It's nice to meet you.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, why are you saying thank you.
Because you taught me how to study...
Because you are my daughter.
Don't cry my baby.
Don't cry..
Mom
Mom, don't cry.. Mom..
Room 11, morning check-in!
You're a furnace.
Just lay down.
You're sick, what are they gonna do?
Hey, hey! What the… just lay down.
Room 10, morning check-in!
Who the hell is laying
down during check-in?
Room 10!
Do I need to send all
of you to solitary confinement?
That's not it...
2037, what are you doing?
Madam
What?
2037 is so sick she can't even sit up.
I think she has to go and see a doctor.
Are you sure?
You sure it's not a misdiagnosis?
Yes, I'm sure.
Don't get up. Just lay down.
I'm so sorry. I got a cold.
Did you know?
What.. Are you talking about?
That you're pregnant.
Stand right there! Stop.
2037.
Hey!! What is this!
Get her!!
Grab her!
Open the door! Open the door!
Mom!
2037!
Let go of me!
How can this be?
She's just a kid! She should be
running around in a school uniform.
Seriously... How far along is she?
They'll find out when
they do an ultrasound.
This is big.
She's going to end up having that baby.
Of course, she'll have the baby.
It's life. What are you gonna do, kill it?
Hey! Bitch!
Think before you speak.
You think it makes
sense to have this baby!
She was sexually assaulted,
Can't she get an abortion?
The wardon went through
the hearing the court's ruling,
Yunyoung beat him to
death with a weapon,
His brain was
literally squashed.
Oh no...
So it's not easy to prove
that is was a sexual assault.
Because of that,
It wasn't ruled as an
act of self-defense,
But rather, bodily
injury resulting in death.
A bastard like that deserves to
get his brain squashed to death,
What's wrong with that?!
That's the law.
You're kidding, right?
So did you end up here
because you followed the law?
Fuck you.
Well, I don't know about the rest of us,
but Yunyoung's different. It not her fault.
Shit. Who out of all of us
isn't being wrongfully accused!!
But there's nothing we can do.
The baby's done nothing
wrong. Yunyoung has to give birth!
Fuck!
The baby is at fault!
It's very existence
itself is wrong, fuck it!
Shit.
Hey!
Why you bitch!
I was nice to you
because you're an orphan.
But now you just act up like
you don't know anything! Shit.
You wanna die?
Great! Go ahead!! Kill me! Go!
You crazy bitch!!
Stop!
You think dying is that easy?
Killing is that easy?
I could kill all of you here tonight,
nothing changes for me.
I'm still the same death row inmate.
Is it the same for you guys? Huh?
Sir!
- Open the door.
- Yes.
Oh no... Now now...
You can't let your heart
freeze up like this..
Baby
Even if it's hard,
you have to push through..
Teacher…
I want to live…
Yes,
You have to.
You have to live well.
Rose...
Rose, This
It ain't easy is it…
Lay down.
Don't do anything, just lay down.
What are you going to do now?
Stop thinking about it
and just take care of it.
Why you!
Are you the mom!
What has the baby done wrong!
Rose, you say something!
Well, it's not a baby yet.
- It's just a fetus.
- Hey!
What a joke!
You guys are all just words,
you can't really be of any help.
Want me to help you?
This is what you do.
Why would you carry such a
son of a bitch in your womb!!
Hey!! Shit. You come here.
You crazy bitch, what are you saying!
What do you think you're doing!
Pitiful bitch!
Once a prostitute and you became a pimp,
so does that make you feel some sympathy?
Since your womb is gone, are you
jealous of the baby or something?
Shit. Yeah, I'm jealous.
I didn't know when I back then.
But since I've lost it I'm jealous!
Shit.
Crazy bitch. Why were you even born?
Fucking bitch.
What are you guys doing fighting here?
Lock'em up!
Feel sorry for what you've done.
If you don't eat, it's only your loss.
Whether you like it or not,
you have to eat to live.
If there's anything you
want to eat, request it.
The warden said
you can use the money in custody.
So don't worry about money.
Why can't I visit? Visit.
Wait…wait
You can take your time.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
Did anything happen to my daughter?
It's nothing like that.
Wait.
Your daughter is refusing all visits.
Why... why...
Why?! My daughter...!
I'm sorry.
There's nothing I can do to help.
I'm sorry. It will be difficult
for you to visit today.
Big Sis told me to bring this to you
because you're not eating anything.
Those bitches.
Hello everyone, nice to see you all.
Wow, you're really pretty.
Can you guys get out?
Our sis wants to talk to this pretty one.
Our sis just wants to have a chat.
Hey, Pretty
I hear you're the youngest ace here.
Do you know me?
Do you really not know our sister?
I'm the bitch from Bulgwang-dong.
I'm the bitch from Ssangmun-dong.
Let's go to the bathroom together.
If I kill you,
this will be my sixth murder
Do you want to watch?
What are you doing, sis?
I told you not to bother
the girls in my room.
Alright, I understand.
I made a mistake.
But you still need to be
punished for ignoring my warning.
I told you to get rid of
the baby not you, bitch.
You don't have the guts to kill
yourself. What's with this fucking shit!
If you can't kill yourself,
Then have the baby!
Abandon it, raise it or kill it,
Do whatever, you fucking bitch!
What is going on!
If 2037 lost her baby, that would
have added murder to your list.
Please don't make trouble here.
Instead of suffering like this,
Why don't we get help from
the press or some civic groups?
If we can get the public opinion on
your side it will be a lot of help to you.
I'm sorry. I don't want to get any help.
Why not?
I mean, we can't even if we wanted to.
Yeah!! You have to get help!
There's the baby!
And you are still so young,
You have to get out of here
as soon as possible and live your life.
I'd rather spend 5 years here.
It would be much more painful to live in shame
hiding from the rest of the world forever.
I'm sure some people will have sympathy
But people will know
I have a baby and that I am a murderer.
And when my frail mom
finds out I am pregnant
She will really die.
She's suffering enough as is.
A mother is much stronger
than you may think.
But I still don't want
My mom getting hurt.
You're right.
As a woman, a normal life is so much better
than one receiving pity from everyone.
Alright then.
Let's put our faith in
a request for retrial.
We should also request for a jury
The jury and the judge will
understand what you're going through.
Then, an abortion will be possible
by proving a sexual assault.
So don't punch your stomach
or hurt yourself in anyway.
Don't. Let's ask them to
push up the retrial date.
Ask who?
Everyone who's awaiting trial,
Thinks their case is urgent and that
their trial date should be pushed up.
Shit. What do we do?
Is the date set for the retrial?
No. But from now on, 2037 will
be in security division work full time.
Why?
It's a special order from
the warden. Let's go.
Can't I just keep working here?
They pay you more than here,
so don't worry and just move.
Besides, it's much easier to go
to the nurse's office from there.
Sir!
Why you!
The work's not that hard.
You open up all the goods
purchased from outside,
And you check to see if
there's anything fishy in there.
If it's medicine, it goes
to the nurse's office.
And the letters go to the different rooms.
Yes.
You can clean a little bit,
And if anyone below me makes
you run errands, you can let me know.
Okay?
Mom, you're doing okay, right?
I couldn't bare to see you.
Just one year, can you wait just one year?
If I work hard and become a model
inmate, they'll even let me study.
Always keep your inhaler nearby.
So Make herbal medicine
and drink it often.
Don't worry about me.
I love you, mom.
You're six months pregnant,
but the baby is very small.
The baby weighs only 300g.
Do you know why?
The baby reads mom's mind.
Because the mom is rejecting the
baby, the baby is hiding away in the womb.
And that's why there's
no changes to your body.
The baby being so small,
will there be health problems?
All the organs and overall
health of the baby good.
And the heartbeat is
very strong, too. Listen.
Yes
Is there anything you want to eat?
Sticky rice cake
Sticky rice cake?
It's okay..
If you're so curious, ask her yourself!
Alright, alright!
What did they say at the hospital?
They said I'm six months along.
Six months?!
Your stomach is not showing
at all but you're six months?
They said the baby is hiding.
Hiding? The baby is hiding in the stomach?
The baby knows how I'm feeling.
Wow. Knows the mother's feelings.
Don't hide. I thought you
lost the baby, I was so worried!
- You should be worried because it's not!
- Shit.
Lila, give this to the youngest.
Sure!
Youngest, our youngest baby.
This will keep you warm. Sleep tight.
Watch it!
Must you wash while I'm in here.
Then stop peeing
I am finished now, you rascal!
Please let me do something.
It's fine. I'll get in trouble.
- I'll do it.
- Go away
Will you stop sptting!
Big sis, this would be clean
enough for the little one, right?
Oh wow, It hasn't been long since
breakfast but you're hungry again.
I'm not hungry.
Someone give her something
to eat. The baby is hungry!
- Am I a prison pantry to you?
- Of course.
Ugh, you stupid bitch.
That's not her being
hungry, it's the baby moving!
Baby moving?
The baby is swimming insdie the womb.
Swim?!
Yes
Visit.
A visit?
Since you've been here
It's your first visit, right?
I don't have anyone to come visit me.
Is that something to be proud of?
Go to the admin office, first.
Good.
Let's pick a bank and
create an account for you.
Why?
Why do I need a bank account?
Ah, well...
Your father's name is Yoo Dongwon, right?
I don't know anyone like that.
Okay. The paper says
your father is Yoo Dongwon.
He was working at a construction
site but he fell and died.
He left behind some
inheritance. About $8000.
I don't need anything like that.
I knew you would say that.
But there's this procedure.
Who else would get the money?
It has to go to a family member.
So just open an account.
You'll be getting some
insurance payment later, too.
You can take care of
that when you get out.
Here, take it.
What about the body?
Oh..Are you curious about it?
They couldn't reach the family,
And he didn't have a home.
It was determined a body with no
affiliation, so they cremated the body.
I solemnly swear that I will
speak the truth under oath.
The prosecution can proceed.
Members of the jury,
The lawful assessment
has shown already that this
Cannot be proven to be
an act of self-defense.
To put it simply
If a thief comes in with a knife,
you can't shoot him dead with a gun.
In other words,
If you use a weapon,
Or if you cause the other person more
harm than the other person did to you,
It can be ruled as excessive self-defense.
Thus,
Even if the defendant
truly was sexually assaulted
Murder cannot be considered
an acceptable retaliation
The jury must also already know
Article 11 sub-paragraph
1 of the Constitution states
All people are equal under law.
This is the logic and
foundation of the law
And critical to society's rules.
Now the defense may proceed.
Your honor, the defendant
would not like to speak further.
Does the defendant not
want to give a final statement?
I will.
I did kill someone.
You don't have to believe me but
I was also sexually assaulted.
I will do as you say.
If the judge says five years, I'll do it. If
the judge says 10 years, I'll do the 10 years.
I will serve my time that you give me
And then return home and live with my mom.
As if this was all a dream,
As if nothing had happened...
I just want to go back to my mom.
But...
For me... this place is so scary
And difficult.
We will now announce the verdict.
The jury's verdict and the
judges' verdict are the same.
We reverse the original verdict.
Even if there was no sexual assault,
And the relation was a consensual one,
It is clear that the encounter
was violent and coercive.
Thus, even though it
cannot be ruled as an act of
Self-defense due to the
severity of the defense,
Given the circumstances,
There is enough reason to
take the situation into account,
And the sentence can be shortened.
However,
Due to the charge of lethal injury,
Defendant Jung Yunyoung
Is sentenced to one year.
A particularly cold winter has gone
by, and spring has arrived at last.
The first song of the day is
"Across the River Spring Arrives"
Hey! Be careful and
at least try to hide it.
If they know you made a knife out of a
nail, you'll go into solitary confinement!
Why do you care, sis?
Did you just call me sis? Wow
You've finally become a human being
now. You can leave this place tomorrow.
Bullshit.
You crazy!
Can we please speak more elegantly?
Bullshit.
Shit, the baby is listening... Shit
I'm so sorry.
Where are you? Wow, the baby's hiding.
Come out. Get some sun, swim freely.
If you have no sense,
at least have some sensitivity.
Are you asking for it?
If only I got caught just a month later,
I wouldn't be here being
humiliated and treated like this.
These ladies got caught for
Prostitution ring!
Pyramid scheme fraud! Violence!
I am not like them.
I am in for adultry. I got caught just a
month before adultery law was abolished.
Wow! You're going to make
a passsing mosquito vomit.
You were seeing three men at once!
Sis, you can't explain love in numbers!
Then how about theft?
Oh, that...
I took their stuff because I was angry
I had to sleep with such scumbags!
Wow, really you're a
total mess, you bitch!
Is there anything you want to eat or do?
No
But I do miss something.
What is it?
I miss cosmos flowers.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
You have to eat a lot of fruit.
It's good for the baby. Here!
I'm ok. I'll pass.
It's not okay. Open up.
You need to gobble it up for the baby.
Youngest
- Can you help me organize my books?
- Sure
Which books should I give you?
You're pregnant, just stay still
I'll help, which book is it?
No! You wouldn't know
one book from another, bitch!
Shit.
I know books! You bitch!
If she went to a 4-year university,
She would've easily been a
pseudo religious cult leader.
I graduated from a 4-year university,
although it was in one of the smaller cities.
4-year universities are only in Seoul!
You absolute idiot!
Get lost!
Shit
Get me the knife.
Why are you giving me bullshit?
Here. Have it.
Really? You love this book.
Yup. I love all of them,
So don't waste precious time and
Use the time for yourself.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh~
Is it possible
Can an ex-convict take the
government employee exam?
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
Clean up.
Let's get your temperature.
It's normal
Any other pain or discomfort
other than your headaches?
I go pee too often,
but other than that, I'm fine.
That part's inevitable
so try to bear with it.
Also taking medicine too often isn't
good for you. Try not to take if you can.
I can't sleep at night
because of the headaches.
It feels like you're coming in to
get the pills too often these days
I will prescribe some medication
for the headaches. Take them here.
I'll take it later,
when I really need it.
Are you hoarding the medication?
No, I really am sick.
Sir!
What are you doing there?
I had headaches so I'm coming
back from seeing the doctor.
Is it really bad?
No, I'm better now.
Okay, so then can we speak for a moment?
Yes
This is chrysathemum tea.
It's good for headaches.
Thank you.
Drink it while it's warm.
Hide it and then have it for yourself.
Thank you also for the
supplements and vitamins.
My youngest daughter is around your age.
So I feel sorry when I see you.
I feel the grown-ups have wronged you.
Let me know if you ever need help.
Also,
why don't you just rest in your room
until you go into labor?
It's more bearable when I move around.
Go ahead, try it.
Mom
Just borrow it and then return it.
Why would you make a needle?
Girl, So that we can keep using it.
Be careful!
You're really good at drawing.
Why do you like cosmos flowers so much?
It's a girl who is shy.
Like my mom.
- The cosmos flowers?
- Yes.
When the flower shakes with the fall wind,
It looks like a shy girl.
Yunyoung must be this pretty
because you takes after your mom.
My mom is way prettier.
Much more prettier!
Oh, by the way!
I asked the warden,
And it turns out five
years after being released,
Ex-convicts can take the
government employee exams.
Really?
Don't loose hope just
because your body is locked up.
Yes.
Look. Cute, huh?
So adorable.
- What's with the color?
- Why?
Do you want the baby to
be dressed as a prisoner?
This is the only fabric I had.
You, go over there and keep watch.
Why?
Shit
This moment we have
to prepare with sincerity
We have to make more
clothes, make more diapers.
And we have to make a comfortable
blanket and pillow, too.
I know it. Pack the thread.
That fearless bitch!
Pack the thread.
Run! Hurry!
What the?
Who did this?
Uh-oh, seems like you'll
go to the punishment room.
Shut up!
Why you crazy bitch!
I'm not crazy.
You said something that got me thinking,
So the baby can't be
wearing prison clothes.
You idiot!
Do you have a brain?
Is my uniform not a
prisoner's uniform?
It is! But today is Sunday.
Sunday is marked red, so pink makes sense.
Ugh, you idiot!
What does pink have to do with Sunday?
They don't really
The baby's going to get scared. Shhh..
Your legs are super sexy.
Are you okay?
You scared the shit out of me.
They said it's just a stomache cramps
so thank goodness.
Using an English name is better, right?
Rose
Tiffany
Natasha
Jessica
If it's a boy, then what?
Of course, it's Daniel Henney.
David, Richard, Michael Johnson.
So what if the name is fancy!
Might as well call it Juju.
All things aside, shouldn't we consult
with Yunyoung about the baby's name?
That's true, But
She hasn't even accepted
the existence of the baby.
She's going through a lot,
so we have to set it up for her,
and when she needs it,
it'll all be ready for her.
How about a Korean name, Bo-ni?
Boni?
Well, the inner skin of a
chestnut is called bo-ni.
It's the part that
protects the fragile inside.
The baby should grow up to be a
person that can protect the weaker ones.
Bo-ni could be for both a girl
and a boy. Not bad at all! Big Sis.
That's right.
No! Hell No!!!
What!!
No, absolutey not. I really really hate it.
Just a husk, dead skin.
It's not dead skin! It doen's mean husk!
It's something that protects the weak and the
fragile. We want the baby to that kind of a person.
Bullshit. What a joke.
Husk! Dead skin!
That's a bad name! It's
just like my life. I hate it.
How about core, huh Big Sis?
- Core! Co-co?
- Co-co-nut?
Bo-ni.
It sounds nice and has a nice meaning.
It's Korean.
I did my own cleaning today.
Hope you'll like these. Cheer up, 2037!
How's this? Is it okay?
This hand is so cute
This one's for the feet.
Wow
So pretty
Shit.
- I'm so tired.
- You haven't done anything.
Yunyoung!
Her water broke!
She's still breathing! Water, water!
Hurry up and bring water!
Yunyoung, wake up!
Guards!! Fucking guards!
Is anyone there? Someone is dying here!
Guards!!
Take deep breaths and push.
Push.
Doctor, she has dilated 10 centimeters
Can you hear me? Push. Push till the end.
You have to push more.
- Please wake up.
- Nurse Push the baby out!
Yes
Patient! Push harder!
At this rate,
it is dangerous for the mother, too.
You have to breathe!
What are you doing?
Are you going to kill the baby?
What is all this?
It's...
All addressed back to this room.
There is too much bleeding.
At this rate, she will go into shock.
Patient Yunyoung Please wake up!
Are you really not going to push?
Both you and the baby could die!
- Push, push!
- Yes.
Patient!
Please wake up.
I'm leaving this letter
in case I don't return.
Teacher, you are hurting, too, right?
You took care of my wounds, and
that helped me keep going forward.
I know you prayed for me, as well.
Thank you so much and I am sorry.
Haesoo sis, I am so sad because I wanted to go
to college and read a lot of books like you.
But I am so happy I got to know you.
When you gave me the history books,
I thought to myself, "I want to give
life and studying another chance."
Thank you for finding out what I liked
without even asking, and helping me so much.
Our troublemaking sis. I'm so
upset I met you so late in life.
I was kind of sad because I felt like you were the only
one who didn't know how much love you hold for others.
You're a great sis, one that
I want to show off to others.
I wish I could stay longer
and pester you. I'm sorry
I relied on you a lot.
And I loved you a lot.
Pretty face, pretty heart, pretty body.
Which is why men won't leave you alone.
But I hope you meet Mr. right who will
love you for who you are and stay with him.
You always looked so pretty to me because you were
ready to love and be loved. I was jealous of that.
I wish I could see you
in your wedding dress.
I have a request for you, cool sis.
When you go out into the world, try growing
your hair and putting on some makeup.
You don't know this but I think
you're the prettiest person I've ever met.
Also, you're not bad
because you were abandoned,
I think it's bad that you
think you were abandoned.
I don't think your parents abandoned you.
I think they protected you.
If I said this to in person, you might
beat me up so I'm writing a letter.
Please, don't hide and
cry anymore. Please!
How is the mother?
It won't be easy but
We have to hope
she'll regain consciousness.
Yunyoung! Mom bought you pizza.
In your next life,
I hope you'll live like a 7-year-old at 7
And a 15-year old when you are 15.
Mommy is so sorry.
Boni, you have to become a pretty girl.
Government employee
Interview certificate
Mom!